Gia Long Bao Hung

DATA ANALYST/BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE

Tan Phu Disctrict • • in

CAREER OBJECTIVES

Finance professional with a strong background in banking, transitioning into data analysis with a focus on business analytics. After completing a 6-month **data analyst certification** at CoderSchool and earning a Master's degree in Finance, I am eager to apply my skills in business data analysis. My goal is to become a senior data analyst within the next 1-2 years, contributing to data-driven decision-making and business growth.

SKILLS & PROJECT

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Analytic Techniques: Data Processing, Descriptive Analytics, Regression Analysis, Time Series Forecasting
- Programming: Python, SQL
- Tools and Visualization: Data Visualization with Seaborn and Matplotlib; Dashboard Building with Power BI

SOFT SKILL: Critical Thinking, Presentation, Problem Solving

PROJECT (Video Included) - Advanced Retail Chain Analysis: Customer Segmentation and Forecasting <a href="https://www.https://www.elga.com/https://www.elga.

EXPERIENCE

Client Services Officer | June 2023 – September 2023

ANZ Bank Vietnam Limited

Responsible for the daily running and management of the Calls and Customers request via mail to ensure customer's call are constantly well managed to resolve customer's problem in a timely manner within the SLA, meeting customer's expectations and achieving customer's delight.

Int'l Settlement Dept- Senior | June 2022 – February 2023

Vietnam Thuong Tin Commercial Joint Stock Bank

- Process Import/Export Letters of Credit, Import/Export Bills, Import/Export-related financing,
 Documentary collection services (DP/DA)
- Submit daily, monthly, semi-annual report to SBV
- Perform all internal report related to data of international payments total sales and charges of Inward & Outward transactions

Trade Operations Officer | November 2019 – April 2022

Vietnam Export Import Commercial Joint - Stock Bank.

Process Import/Export Letters of Credit, Import/Export Bills, Import/Export-related financing,
 Documentary collection services (DP/DA)

EDUCATION

DataScience Track - CoderSchool - Graduation 2024

- Intensive course (20+ hours per week) focusing on fundamentals of Data Analysis with Python, SQL, statistical techniques, and machine learning models
- Practice hands-on Data Analysis project with real-world application

Master's degree - University of Economics Ho Chi Minh City - Graduation 2024

Bachelor's degree - HOA SEN University - Graduation 2018

IELTS - IDP International - Graduation 2018

IELTS 6.0/9